<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on The Inner Circle Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.theinnercircle.lol/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on The Inner Circle Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 15:55:43 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.theinnercircle.lol/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why make a website?</title>
      <link>https://blog.theinnercircle.lol/posts/why-make-a-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 15:55:43 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.theinnercircle.lol/posts/why-make-a-website/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The purpose&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;Many of you may be wondering, why bother creating a website? Just use social media! Well, a website will always be mine, the domain will always be mine as long as I pay the registrar, it can&amp;rsquo;t be taken away from me as long as I manage the website. This is my personal online journal, my life story and my progress as well as accountability for projects. If I don&amp;rsquo;t have anyone to hold me accountable for projects, if I don&amp;rsquo;t have even the sense of accountability, I just won&amp;rsquo;t complete them, and this one was completed due to the visibility of my Discord server and the visibility of the entire internet.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Beginning of the TIC Blog!</title>
      <link>https://blog.theinnercircle.lol/posts/the-beginning-of-the-tic-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 15:55:43 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.theinnercircle.lol/posts/the-beginning-of-the-tic-blog/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here we are, the beginning of my web admin/creation journey, building a nice (albeit very basic) blog for my discord group! This is an extremely early prototype blog and essentially a proof of concept, but I&amp;rsquo;ll be working on this in the future and will hopefully have regular updates whenever I&amp;rsquo;m available to post.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The idea came from a NetworkChuck video about creating a blog/website that you own based on custom domains that you have purchased. I love this guy&amp;rsquo;s videos, and while some of them are obvious plugs for a service or product, he tries to integrate useful and somewhat meaningful ideas into his content, and that&amp;rsquo;s something I feel YouTube sorely needs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
